bookgift.us 2006-10-05

# Bookgift.Us :: Privacy Policy

_**Privacy Policy Statement  
**_

This site is hosted in USA. Our software store pages, ordering system, and order data. The software automatically collects order information but may only use this information in its total form. If you accessed this store through a Shopping network, the network may also automatically collect information about your shopping experience. Please see the Privacy Policy of accessing network for more information about how they use this information.

**SUMMARY STATEMENT**

We respect your privacy.   
Effective Jul/03/2003  
Privacy Notice Table of Contents:  
• Our Commitment to Privacy  
• The Information We Collect  
• How We Use Information  
• Our Commitment to Data Security  
• Our Commitment to Children's Privacy  
• How to Access or Correct Your Information  
• How to Contact Us

**Our Commitment to Privacy  
**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. The Information We Collect: This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Bookgoft.us web site. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name Address Email address Phone number Credit/Debit Card Information  
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are Name Address Phone Number  
Our web master has signed a statement that no program in the site enables the designer or programmer any access to the customer information.

**The Way We Use Information:  
**  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We offer gift-cards by which you can personalize a product you order for another person. Information you provide to us to create a gift-card is only used for that purpose, and it is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our web site if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our web site will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our web site and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our web site, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

  **Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our web site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our web site is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access or Correct**

Your Information You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by [description of the company access procedure]. We use this procedure to safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How to Contact Us  
**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1815 642 9301 or send us an email at [ privacy@bookgift.us](mailto:privacy@bookgift.us).

* * *
